<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<includes>
  <include name="SetupGuide">
    <label>[B][COLOR button_focus]Welcome to the FENtastic Setup Guide[/COLOR][/B]

FENtastic is a skin specifically designed for FEN users. It can display movie, tvshow, and episode widgets as well as submenu widgets. It can also set paths for main menu items (more on this later). Here in this guide I will show you how these work and how to set them up.

On first install the home screen should be empty. This means that the Movie and Show sections should be missing from the main menu on the left.

Now lets go set up the widgets.
From this dialog screen click Back on your remote or Backspace if you are using a keyboard. Here you'll see a group of menu items on the left. Navigate up to Main menu items. Here is where we will set up the widgets. 

Click a menu item to toggle the display of a section on and off. This will show or hide the section on the home screen. Now toggle the Movie/Show section to 'on'. You'll see a group of menu items drop down. They are main menu path, set widgets, category widget (top), and category widget (bottom).

[B][COLOR deeppink]- Set main menu path[/COLOR][/B] is for setting up the path when clicking on the Movie/Show section in the main menu on the left side of the home screen. You can set this to whatever you path you like within FEN. I like to set mine to my Trakt movie/tvshow collection.

[B][COLOR deeppink]- Set widgets[/COLOR][/B] is for setting up the movie/tvshow widgets. These are the main widgets that you'll set up. You can configure up to 10 movie and 10 TV show widgets. After choosing a path you'll have the option to set the label and display type (Poster or Landscape) for each widget. There is also a custom display type for episodes.

[B][COLOR deeppink]- Set category widget (top/bottom)[/COLOR][/B] is for setting up the category widgets. These are submenu-like widgets that point to a list of shortcuts for FEN. These widgets will sandwich your main movie/tvshow widgets. You can choose one submenu for the top and one for the bottom for both movies and tvshows. I recommend setting these to folders within FEN such as Genres, Years, etc. For greater flexibility you can also display custom curated Shortcut folders from FEN. This way you'll be able to set every single item in the submenu. To learn how to set these up go to the FEN addon » Tools » Tips for Fen Use » Shortcut Folders.

That's it! You're all set to go. Enjoy the skin!
    </label>
  </include>
</includes>