<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<includes>
  <include name="Changelog">
    <label>[B][COLOR accent_color]Version $INFO[System.AddonVersion(skin.fentastic)][/COLOR][/B]
- Fixed ratings not showing on some items
- Readded Embuary Helper/Info functionality to Video Info window

[COLOR red][B]Please make sure to clear the ratings cache and restart Kodi before trying to fetch ratings again.[/B][/COLOR]

[B][COLOR accent_color]Version 1.0.21[/COLOR][/B]
- Switched ratings source to MDbList for better tvshow support (enter MDbList API Key in Skin settings to activate)
- Created Ratings section in Skin settings
- Added on/off toggles for individual ratings
- Added high quality icons for ratings
- Added optional one-click trailers (requires MDbList API Key)
- Added IMDb popular ratings. These are from IMDb's most popular movies and tvshows. The rating for these is out of 100. The color coding of the new flame icon is as follows:

  • [COLOR blueviolet][B]PURPLE[/B][/COLOR] flame = Top 10
  • [COLOR deeppink][B]PINK[/B][/COLOR] flame = Top third (10 - 33)
  • [COLOR darkorange][B]ORANGE[/B][/COLOR] flame = Middle third (33 - 66)
  • [COLOR dodgerblue][B]BLUE[/B][/COLOR] flame = Bottom third (66 - 100)

[B]IMPORTANT: After you have entered in your MDbList API key, I HIGHLY recommend clicking the "Clear ratings cache" button in Skin settings and then restarting Kodi before trying to fetch new ratings again. If you do not do this you may run into errors. This is a one time thing that will minimize the possibility of running into issues related to the switch to MDbList.[/B]

- Added optional one-click close of Kodi via the homescreen power button. If you decide to use this you can still access the shutdown menu by holding the back key/backspace on your remote/keyboard.
- Other changes/fixes

[B][COLOR accent_color]Version 1.0.20[/COLOR][/B]
- Fixed crashing bug. You can now enable ReuseLanguageInvoker in FEN.
- Added overlay for background media playback
- Added network sources for choosing of custom background
- Removed [B]Tip: Crashes[/B] window

[B][COLOR accent_color]Version 1.0.19[/COLOR][/B]
- Updated UI for a more artwork centric experience
- Updated widgets to handle menu items better
- Added 3 NEW custom main menu sections
- Added ratings (enter MDbList API Key in Skin settings to activate)
- Added switch for Landscape/Clearlogo on WideList view
- Added custom default background selection
- Added optional color studio logos
- Added custom background and fanart brightness
- Added custom version of AutoCompletion for virtual keyboard to repo (only try if you are having issues with your version)
- Added optional FENtastic Audio Suite to repo
- Reorganized skin settings
- Fixed WideWall view
- Removed color themes
- Other changes/fixes

[B][COLOR accent_color]Version 1.0.18[/COLOR][/B]
- Small bug fix

[B][COLOR accent_color]Version 1.0.17[/COLOR][/B]
- Brought back optional alternate InfoPanel
- Brought back %, progress is now shown as '33% watched' instead of '33'
- Added air date to InfoPanel for episodes
- Made icon silhouettes for category widgets optional
- Other small changes/fixes

[B][COLOR accent_color]Version 1.0.16[/COLOR][/B]
- Added BigPoster, BigLandscape, and BigLandscapeInfo widget display types
- Updated Wall views to use bigger artwork
- Increased visibility of raindrop background
- Added icon silhouettes to category widgets
- Added titles for movies/tvshows/episodes to widget labels
- Added MPAA ratings to InfoPanel for movies/tvshows/episodes
- Added studios to InfoPanel for tvshows/episodes
- Added runtime to InfoPanel for movies/episodes
- Added total seasons to InfoPanel for tvshows
- Added Ends at: to InfoPanel for episodes
- Added percent progress to Landscape widgets for episodes
- Added optional focus animations for main menu, widgets, and views
- Removed %, progress is now shown as '33' instead of '33%'
- Removed alternate InfoPanel
- Fixed profile change bug

[B][COLOR accent_color]Version 1.0.15[/COLOR][/B]
- Small bug fix for TRAKT search widget

[B][COLOR accent_color]Version 1.0.14[/COLOR][/B]
- Extensive overhaul of UI. There are some parts of the skin that I don't use so if something looks off, please let me know by opening an issue in my Github repo
- Fixed blank Search window on new Kodi installs
- Fixed stacked widget renaming
- Updated widget list to circular ordering; topmost widget will now cycle to the bottom when moved up and vice versa
- Added colored frame highlight for focused widget items
- Moved progress back to focused items for widgets, removed progress from InfoPanel
- Added tvshow progress to LandscapeInfo widgets
- Changed TRAKT search widget to stacked type
- Updated Github documentation to reflect new UI changes
- Other fixes/changes

[B][COLOR accent_color]Version 1.0.13[/COLOR][/B]
- Added functionality for:
  • Rearranging and renaming widgets
  • Renaming main menu labels
  • Changing widget display types
  • Click a current widget/menu path for options
- Dynamic labels for movies/TV shows in Skin settings
- Simplified widget/menu dialog headers
- Optional Search results window with custom search history. 
  • Search multiple categories simultaneously
  • Added opening options for Search results window
    - Choose between Open keyboard and Open search window
    - Activate in Skin settings » Options
  • Quick access to TRAKT lists via button
- Reactivated Shift view
- Other changes/fixes

[B][COLOR accent_color]Version 1.0.12[/COLOR][/B]
- Added customizable load delay for stacked widgets. You can find this new setting in Skin settings » Options
- Added optional display of countdown timer for use with the stacked widget load delay
- Added toggle for auto-scrolling labels on LandscapeInfo widgets
- Cleaned up LandscapeInfo widget for episodes

[B][COLOR accent_color]Version 1.0.11[/COLOR][/B]
- Quick fix for stacked widgets not loading on startup

[B][COLOR accent_color]Version 1.0.10[/COLOR][/B]
- Resized all Poster, Landscape, and LandscapeInfo widgets
- Resized PVR, Addon, and Favorites widgets
- Resized artwork for InfoWall, WideInfoWall, Wall, WideWall, and Poster views
- Moved progress for List view to top of poster
- Removed Shift view from movie/tvshow content
- Refactored progress bars across all views
- Added thumbnails to Path selection in Helper
- Fixed label still showing when empty widget was collapsed
- Fixed longer titles not scrolling in LandscapeInfo widgets
- Fixed widget sorting behavior
- Added new detailed documentation for skin setup to Github repo

[B][COLOR accent_color]Version 1.0.9[/COLOR][/B]
- Small fixes

[B][COLOR accent_color]Version 1.0.8[/COLOR][/B]
- Added custom category widgets. You are no longer limited to top and bottom category widgets
- Added optional stacked category widgets
- Added Clear Path option for Main Menu paths and category widgets
- Updated Setup Guide
- Moved ratings to upper right corner of artwork
- Cleaned up season views
- Adjusted background transparency skin-wide. I don't use all parts of the skin so if some colors look off in a particular area of the skin please let me know by opening an issue on my Github
- Small text alignment changes to PVR guide
- Removed widget limits (Set limits for addon and widgets in FEN settings)
- Removed startup video (Total skin size is now under 7 MB)
- Other small fixes/changes

[B][COLOR accent_color]Version 1.0.7[/COLOR][/B]
- Re-added changelog viewing for other addons
- Reverted focus and scrolling behavior for widgets that don't use the InfoPanel
- Added details to Available updates category widget. You can now see how many addon updates are pending directly from the Addon section on the home screen
- Added tip to Extra info to help with Kodi crashes

[B][COLOR accent_color]Version 1.0.6[/COLOR][/B]
- Added optional Raindrop Animated Background. You can turn this off in Skin settings » Options » Raindrop background. Note: Only works when you have Show media background toggled to 'off' in Skin settings » Artwork
- Moved percent progress for widgets to InfoPanel
- Changed widget scrolling behavior
- Fixed Landscape widget for episodes
- Fixed Episode widget for movies and tvshows
- Renamed Episode widget to LandscapeInfo
- Other small fixes/changes

[B][COLOR accent_color]Version 1.0.5[/COLOR][/B]
- Fixed scrolling in changelog and setup guide windows

[B][COLOR accent_color]Version 1.0.4[/COLOR][/B]

[B]IMPORTANT NOTICE: IF YOUR WIDGETS WERE DELETED AFTER THIS UPDATE PLEASE READ INFO BELOW

In this version the default widgets that you may have seen on first install have been removed. In order to avoid possible future conflicts and/or errors, please go to Skin settings » Main menu items » click Remake Menus and Widgets. This will remove the default widgets if any and remake the ones you have already set up. If you didn't set up any widgets on first install, and all of your widgets were deleted, go back into Skin settings » Main menu items in order to set up your widgets. See Setup Guide for help setting up your widgets. This is a one-time thing and will not be necessary for future updates.[/B]

- Added release year to InfoPanel
- Changed default format of InfoPanel. You can switch back to the previous format by going into Skin settings » Options » Alternate Format (InfoPanel)
- Renamed Changelog tab in Skin settings to Extra info
- Added Setup Guide to Extra info

[B][COLOR accent_color]Version 1.0.3[/COLOR][/B]
- Added new InfoPanel for movie, show, and episode widgets
- Moved startup video and widget limit settings to new Options tab in Skin settings
- Small adjustments to most views
- Cleaned up collections info panel
- Small fixes/changes

[B][COLOR accent_color]Version 1.0.2[/COLOR][/B]
- Added changelog to Skin settings menu

[B][COLOR accent_color]Version 1.0.1[/COLOR][/B]
- Re-added startup video (Recommended to test with lower volume)
- Made startup video optional
- Added screenshots

[B][COLOR accent_color]Version 1.0.0[/COLOR][/B]
- Added adjustable widget limits for movies/shows and episodes

[B][COLOR accent_color]Version 0.0.9[/COLOR][/B]
- Small fixes/changes

[B][COLOR accent_color]Version 0.0.8[/COLOR][/B]
- Removed startup video

[B][COLOR accent_color]Version 0.0.7 (Initial release)[/COLOR][/B]
Main changes from default Estuary include:
- 2 NEW viewtypes ("WideWall" and "WideInfoWall")
- Plenty of adjustments to pre-existing views
- New default Colors theme
- New Color theme 'purple'
- Skin-wide adjustments to dialog and menu colors for every Color theme
- Progress displayed for movies, shows, seasons and episodes
- Customizable movie and show main menu items
- Customizable widgets and category widgets for movies, shows, and episodes
- Custom Search options from Home window
- PVR guide adjustments
- Nexus themed startup video
    </label>
  </include>


  <include name="SetupGuide">
    <label>[B][COLOR accent_color]Welcome to the FENtastic Setup Guide[/COLOR][/B]

FENtastic is a skin specifically designed for FEN users. It can display movie, tvshow, and episode widgets as well as submenu widgets. It can also set paths for main menu items (more on this later). Here in this guide I will show you how these work and how to set them up.

On first install the home screen should be empty. This means that the Movie and Show sections should be missing from the main menu on the left.

Now lets go set up the widgets.
From this dialog screen click Back on your remote or Backspace if you are using a keyboard. Here you'll see a group of menu items on the left. Navigate up to Main menu items. Here is where we will set up the widgets. 

Click a menu item to toggle the display of a section on and off. This will show or hide the section on the home screen. Now toggle the Movie/Show section to 'on'. You'll see a couple of menu items drop down. They are set main menu path and set widgets.

[B][COLOR deeppink]- Set main menu path[/COLOR][/B] is for setting up the path when clicking on the Movie/Show section in the main menu on the left side of the home screen. You can set this to whatever you path you like within FEN. I like to set mine to my Trakt movie/tvshow collection.

[B][COLOR deeppink]- Set widgets[/COLOR][/B] is for setting up the movie/tvshow widgets. These are the main widgets that you'll set up. You can configure up to 10 movie and 10 TV show widgets. After choosing a path you'll have the option to set the label and display type (Poster, Landscape, LandscapeInfo, and Category) for each widget. If you choose the Category display type, you'll have the option to set it up as a stacked widget. After that you can choose the display type for the stacked widget as well.

[B][COLOR accent_color]Stacked widgets[/COLOR][/B] contain a category widget and a normal widget beneath. The category widget "communicates" with the normal widget in order to load the new widget list according to the focused item in the category widget. If the stacked widget that you set up has 20 items in it, then that means you'll be able to have all 20 widgets available from just one widget on the home screen.

That's it! You're all set to go. Enjoy the skin!

If you would like to see a more detailed version of this Setup Guide, please visit my Github repo at https://github.com/ivarbrandt/skin.fentastic
    </label>
  </include>
</includes>